ecommercepartners.net 2013-04-16

# Privacy | ECommerce Partners

Home > ECommerce Partners, Inc. Privacy Policy

(last revised: January 28, 2008) 

ECommerce Partners, Inc. is a company that helps other businesses operate sweepstakes, contests and promotions ("Promotions"). In addition, ECommerce Partners occasionally runs its own Promotions. Such Promotions gather personally identifiable information from those individuals who choose to enter a particular Promotion and anonymous data regarding the Promotion itself. ECommerce Partners takes its privacy obligations both to its clients and to people who enter its Promotions very seriously. ECommerce Partners adheres to the Safe Harbor Principles as established by the European Commission and the United States Department of Commerce. 

This policy outlines our treatment of personally identifiable information we collect on behalf of our clients and for our own use. There are three types of Promotions in which ECommerce Partners is involved:

  * **Client Promotions;**
  * **ECommerce Partners "Opt-in" to Client Promotions;**
  * **ECommerce Partners Promotions.**

**Client Promotions:** As a full service promotions and sweepstakes agency, ECommerce Partners operates Promotions on behalf of its clients. As part of those services, ECommerce Partners collects personally identifiable information for its clients by use of ECommerce Partners' proprietary online technology, ECommerce Partners mailboxes, and points of entry offline. ECommerce Partners collects such personally identifiable information solely for the use of its clients and the operation of the Promotions. ECommerce Partners does not use any of the data collected itself, other than to notify potential winners and for prize fulfillment purposes in connection with a Promotion.

ECommerce Partners does not consolidate data across different clients' Promotions, does not maintain data beyond the conclusion of client Promotions (other than for back-up purposes on its client's behalf), and does not "monetize" data collected on behalf of its clients in any manner whatsoever. ECommerce Partners strictly limits access to all personally identifiable information within its organization, and data is never shared outside of the company for any reason whatsoever (with, of course, the exception of appropriate governmental or legal requests). Personally identifiable information collected from different client Promotions is never mingled or shared with anyone other than the client on whose behalf the information was collected. Personally identifiable information collected by ECommerce Partners on behalf of a client belongs solely to the client and will be used solely in accordance with that particular client's Privacy Policy.

An individual's desire to "opt-out" of receiving marketing or other information from a client will be handled in accordance with a particular client's Privacy Policy. ECommerce Partners requires its clients, by contract, to use the data which ECommerce Partners collects on its behalf in accordance with generally accepted privacy standards for both offline and online data, which includes an "opt-out" method for individuals who have provided personally identifiable information. Ultimately, however, ECommerce Partners is not responsible for data collected on behalf of its clients when such data is in its client's possession. Where ECommerce Partners operates one Promotion on behalf of multiple clients, the use of the personally identifiable information by all of the companies involved will be clearly outlined by a Privacy Policy created for that Promotion.

**ECommerce Partners "Opt-in" to Client Promotions:** From time to time, ECommerce Partners and one of its clients will agree to allow ECommerce Partners to offer entrants to a Promotion an opportunity to "opt-in" to receiving marketing information from ECommerce Partners and its partners. In such cases, on the Promotion registration page, an ECommerce Partners "opt-in" question will appear clearly explaining to potential entrants that by checking the box they will be agreeing to share their personally identifiable information with ECommerce Partners. If there is not an ECommerce Partners "opt-in" question on the registration form, ECommerce Partners will not share or use any of the data collected whatsoever. When individuals "opt-in" to receive information from ECommerce Partners, they are agreeing to receive email and other notices from ECommerce Partners, including marketing messages, surveys, special offers and notices about other Promotions. Such notices may come from ECommerce Partners itself, companies with whom ECommerce Partners has a business relationship and/or ECommerce Partners clients.

**Opting Out** If you want to "opt-out" of receiving such notices from ECommerce Partners after you have "opted-in", or you wish to correct the information you have provided to ECommerce Partners, you may do so in one of two (2) ways:

  * Please send email to [remove[at]ECommercePartners.net](mailto:remove@ECommercePartners.net). Please make sure to include the name of the promotion in the subject line and in the body of the email from which you wish to opt-out. Failure to provide this information may delay the processing of your request.
  * Mail the details of your request to:
  * Privacy Policy c/o ECommerce Partners, Inc.
  * 59 Franklin Street, 6th Floor
  * New York, NY 10013 

**ECommerce Partners Promotions:** ECommerce Partners also runs Promotions on its own behalf. Such Promotions are to generate interest from other businesses in ECommerce Partners' products and services. ECommerce Partners uses the personally identifiable information collected in such Promotions as sales leads and may contact the individual registrants by email, mail or phone to discuss the registrant's interest in retaining ECommerce Partners. ECommerce Partners will never sell such information, share it with another business, or use it for any purpose other than marketing ECommerce Partners own core business. If you want to "opt-out" of being contacted by ECommerce Partners after you have participated in one of its Promotions, or you wish to correct the information you have provided to ECommerce Partners, you may do so in one of two (2) ways:

  * Please send email to [remove@ECommercepartners.net](mailto:remove@ECommercePartners.net). Please make sure to include the name of the promotion in the subject line and in the body of the email from which you wish to opt-out. Failure to provide this information may delay the processing of your request.
  * Mail the details of your request to: 
  * Privacy Policy ECommerce Partners, Inc. 
  * 59 Franklin Street, 6th th Floor 
  * New York, NY 10013 

**ECommerce Partners' Online Promotion Technology:** ECommerce Partners' proprietary Promotion technology has the ability to collect data other than personally identifiable information for any of the three (3) kinds of Promotions it operates online. ECommerce Partners may collect information about your computer configuration, such as your browser type, operating system, or ISP domain name. ECommerce Partners may collect information about the site you last visited prior to the Promotion or about your activity during your visit to the Promotion site. This information will not reveal your personal identity (it is anonymous), may be used by ECommerce Partners to administer the technical and operational aspects of this site, and may include using your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server. Your IP address may also be used to gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. ECommerce Partners may use a cookie, a piece of data stored on the user's hard drive containing information about the user, to assist in performing some or all of these activities and also to limit your ability to play a Promotion more times than allowed. You can set your browser to accept all, some, or no cookies. If you set your browser to reject all cookies, you may be limited in your ability to access some, or all aspects of a particular Promotion. 

**Special Note about Children:** Unless otherwise specifically indicated, ECommerce Partners Promotions are not available to anyone under the age of thirteen (13). ECommerce Partners does, however, operate some Promotions on behalf of its clients which collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen (13). In each such instance, ECommerce Partners and its clients comply fully with all aspects of the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act ("COPPA") in the operation of the Promotion, in the collection of the information itself and in the subsequent use of the data collected. Personally identifiable information will not be collected from children under the age of thirteen (13) without parental consent in compliance with the COPPA guidelines. 

**Your California Privacy Rights (As provided by California Civil Code Section 1798.83):** A California resident who has provided personal information to a business with whom he/she has established a business relationship for personal, family, or household purposes ("California customer") is entitled to request information about whether the business has disclosed personal information to any third parties for the third parties' direct marketing purposes. In general, if the business has made such a disclosure of personal information, upon receipt of a request by a California customer, the business is required to provide a list of all third parties to whom personal information was disclosed in the preceding calendar year, as well as a list of the categories of personal information that were disclosed.

However, under the law, a business is not required to provide the above-described lists if the business adopts and discloses to the public (in its privacy policy) a policy of not disclosing customer's personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes unless the customer first affirmatively agrees to the disclosure, as long as the business maintains and discloses this policy. Rather, the business may comply with the law by notifying the customer of his or her right to prevent disclosure of personal information and providing a cost free means to exercise that right.

**Contact ECommerce Partners:** If you wish to contact ECommerce Partners to correct, amend, or delete information (if ECommerce Partners is holding on to your information as explained above), about privacy related issues or for any reason at all, you may do so in one of two (2) ways

  * 1\. Mail to: 
  * Privacy Policy ECommerce Partners, Inc.
  * 59 Franklin Street, 6th FL
  * New York, NY 10013 or 
  * 2\. Email to: [privacy[at]ECommercePartners.net](mailto:privacy@ECommercePartners.net)
  * 

**Material Changes to Policy:** ECommerce Partners may make material changes to this Privacy Policy from time to time. Therefore, you should periodically visit this page to view the current Privacy Policy. In the event of a material change to this Privacy Policy, ECommerce Partners shall send an email advising of the change to all persons whose email addresses we have collected and retained pursuant to the terms set forth above.

ECommerce Partners, Inc. takes very seriously the private nature of your personal information. This Privacy Policy describes how we treat the information we collect when you visit our Web site and/or register for our email updates. Please read this notice carefully. 

**Personal Information** In order to supply you with your ECommerce Partners, Inc. e-mail, we need your e-mail address. Similarly, in order to supply you with text messaging services, we need your phone number and your provider information. So that we may provide you with additional services, we may also request your name, geographical coordinates, and telephone number. ECommerce Partners, Inc. does not collect any other personal information that you do not expressly provide. ECommerce Partners, Inc. will never sell, rent or share your personal information, including your e-mail address, with any third parties for marketing purposes without your express permission. ECommerce Partners, Inc.may share your personal information for the purpose of delivering our e-mail to you or as required by law. 

**Non-Personal Information** We may also request non-personally identifiable information, such as [birth date, buying preferences, or age], also known as demographic and profile data, though this information is optional. We may use this data to improve our site and/or tailor your experience at our site, showing you content that we think you might be interested in, and displaying content according to your preferences. We may also share this information with others, such as advertisers interested in advertising in the ECommerce Partners, Inc. or our site, in aggregate, anonymous form, which means that the information will not contain any personally identifiable information about you or any other person.

**Usage Information** In addition to collecting personal and non-personal information, ECommerce Partners, Inc. may also collect non-personal, aggregated information about subscribers' use of our site. This information is not personally identifiable and will only be used to find out how subscribers use our service and site. For example, this information will tell us how much time users spend on our site, from which other sites subscribers came, and to what other sites subscribers go. The collection of this information allows us to, among other things, prepare for traffic load demands and to efficiently deliver information to you..

**Review and Access** Upon your request, we will provide you with a summary of the information we collect about you. You will have an opportunity to correct, update or modify this information.

**Choice/Opt-Out** If we ever send you information by e-mail concerning new products or services that you did not expressly request, we will provide you with an e-mail address by which you may request no future notices.

**Tracking** Like most sites, ECommerce Partners, Inc. makes use of browser "cookies." Cookies are small text files placed on your computer's hard disk by our server. They allow us to quickly check your status as a subscriber and facilitate access to your preferences. ECommerce Partners, Inc. will never use cookies to retrieve information from a computer that is unrelated to our site or services. 

**Links to Other Sites** As part of the service, ECommerce Partners, Inc. may create links allowing you to access third party sites. ECommerce Partners, Inc. is not responsible for the content that appears on those sites and does not endorse these sites. Please consult those sites' individual privacy policies in order to determine how they treat user information.

**Security** All information described above is stored on restricted database servers.

**Modification to this Policy** ECommerce Partners, Inc. may change this policy, but we'll post any changes here, be sure to check in.

**Contact Us** If you have any questions about this policy or our site in general, please contact us. (info[at]ecommercepartners.net)
